Hello friends, welcome to the comment section. We will
talk about Torrent Pharma in the share market.
So, let's discuss the corporate of this company in detail. So,
let's cover in detail how the
company's results were the day before yesterday.
Friends, this company has the most
important point. If we talk about the
company's revenue for operations first of all, then
this company has 60 crores. Subscribe,
like and subscribe. Now let's talk about the total
revenue of this company in the top 10 companies of all time. We will
write here a little bit about the
total expenses of this company.
This brother can't
record last year was 1500 crores. The
total expenses of this company have also increased.
This device has been revised and a
decline has been seen in this also.
After that, let's talk about the company's point of this
contest. So, for quite well, the
company has made it official here, which
in the last quarter we had 301 crores
last year. If we talk about Indian card, then
here
we have a good positive of the company.  The
company has increased its quarterly revision as
well, apart from that Yudhishthir also, but we will talk about the
net profit of the company, Bigg Boss, after
deducting all the taxes etc. of the company,
how much is the profit of the main company, then that piece 724 crores,
which is the last year 2008 crores,
so here if you
talk about the overall pocket of the password company, then there has been a problem in the
quarterly, the deposit of the company is less
and there has been a decline in this matter,
apart from that, talking
about the sales of the company here, ₹15 121
paise went to the company, then
1658 paise from the court, if we talk about last year, then
last year if ₹70 60% or Arvind of the company,
our
volume has decreased from yesterday, so friends, these were the
results of the company, here the
revenue voucher of the company has increased a bit,
but talking about profit, here a
lot of decline has been seen in the office of the company,
apart from that, the company's caring has also decreased a lot,
that Bigg Boss, how do you know this  If you liked it, please
tell me by commenting. Apart from this, if you are not happy then
please subscribe to my channel
and do not forget to press the bell icon.